opencartextensions.in 2016-12-02

# Privacy Policy | Opencart Extensions No 1. India

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Opencart Extensions, Opencart Modules collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://www.opencartextensions.in/ website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by Opencart Extensions , Opencart Modules.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site place an order fill out a form subscribe to the newsletter and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number,  
We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Web browser cookies**

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly.

**Use License**

Permission is granted to temporarily download one copy of the materials (information or software) on opencartextensions's web site for personal, non-commercial transitory viewing only. This is the grant of a license, not a transfer of title, and under this license you may not:

        i.     modify or copy the materials;

        ii.   use the materials for any commercial purpose, or for any public display (commercial or non-commercial);

        iii.  attempt to decompile or reverse engineer any software contained on opencartextensions's web site;

        iv.   remove any copyright or other proprietary notations from the materials; or

        v.    transfer the materials to another person or "mirror" the materials on any other server.

This license shall automatically terminate if you violate any of these restrictions and may be terminated by opencartextensions at any time. Upon terminating your viewing of these materials or upon the termination of this license, you must destroy any downloaded materials in your possession whether in electronic or printed format.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site. 

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. We may use third party service providers to help us operate our business and the Site or administer activities on our behalf, such as sending out newsletters or surveys. We may share your information with these third parties for those limited purposes provided that you have given us your permission 

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:Website Name: Opencart Extensions , Opencart Moduleshttp://www.opencartextensions.in/Phone no: +91-161-5012104email to contact: info@opencartextensions.in
